(Sheldon:)...Miscellaneous Duties,
you are obligated to take me to the dentist.
See? Here, after "providing a confirmation
sniff on questionable dairy products."
You know what?
I am sick of the Roommate Agreement.
(Leonard:)It's ridiculous, I'm your roommate,
not your chauffeur.
(Leonard:)I had better things to do yesterday...
...than drive you to the good
model train store in Garden Grove...
(Leonard:)...because the one in Pasadena
has gotten too big for its britches.
(Sheldon:)Well, it has. Ask anybody.
(Leonard:)I don't care. I'm done.
(Sheldon:)Hold on. Are you saying that
you want to invoke Clause 209?
(Leonard:)I don't know what that is, but if it means
I can go home and sleep, then yes.
(Sheldon:)Think carefully here.
Clause 209 suspends our friendship...
...and strips the Roommate Agreement
to its essentials.
(Sheldon:)Our responsibilities toward
each other would be rent...
(Sheldon:)...utilities and a perfunctory chin jut
of recognition as we pass in the hall.
What's up?